hinchcliffe.org 2014-12-05

# Privacy

_Last Updated: June 27, 2014_.

This policy covers Sprinklr’s privacy practices for our public website, accessible at [http://www.sprinklr.com](http://www.sprinklr.com/).

To read policies relating to our and our customer’s use of the Sprinklr platform or other Sprinklr products, [please click here](http://www.sprinklr.com/social-media-management-system-privacy-policy/ "Social Media Management System Privacy Policy").

**We Respect the Privacy of Visitors to Our Website.**

We have developed this website Privacy Policy to clearly and transparently communicate what information we collect, how we collect it and what we do with it.

This website Privacy Policy applies only to the operation of websites that directly link to this policy when you click on “Privacy Policy” in the website footer.

_BY REGISTERING ON OR SUBMITTING INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY._

**TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Your Identifiable Information.**

Through this website we may collect information that can identify you (“Identifiable Information”) when it is voluntarily submitted to us. Your Identifiable Information includes:

•    Your name;  
•    Your address;  
•    Your telephone number;  
•    Your email address;   
•    Your IP address; and,  
•    Other similar information.

**Non-Identifiable Information.**

We may also automatically collect other non-identifiable information in connection with your visit to this website (“Non-Identifiable Information”). We usually collect Non-Identifiable Information through the use of cookies, web beacons or other anonymous tracking technologies (see below).

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**

**Information Voluntarily Provided to Us.**

_We collect any information voluntarily provided to us._ This includes any Identifiable Information or Non-Identifiable Information that you provide to us (for example, by submitting such information into forms on our website or by emailing the information to us).

_A Note About Your IP Address:_

_We automatically collect your IP Address._

Our website uses Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses to track your visit to our site. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP) so you can access the Internet. Generally, an IP address changes each time you connect to the Internet (it is a “dynamic” address).

Note, however, that if you have a broadband connection, depending on your individual circumstance, it is possible that the IP Address that we collect, or even perhaps a cookie we use (see “Cookies” below), may contain information that could be deemed identifiable. This is because with some broadband connections your IP Address doesn’t change (it is “static”) and could be associated with your personal computer. We use your IP address to report aggregate information on use and to help improve the website.

**Information We Automatically Collect With Web Beacons.**

This site may use a technology known as web beacons – sometimes called single pixel gifs – that allow this site to collect web log information. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an email message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered when you visit one of our websites by the computer that hosts our website (called a “web server”). The web server automatically recognizes some non-personal information, such as the date and time you visited our site, the pages you visited, the website you came from, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 2008), and the domain name and address of your ISP (e.g., Comcast). We may also include web beacons in promotional email messages in order to determine whether messages have been opened.

**Information We Automatically Collect With Cookies.**

This website may use a technology called a “cookie”. A cookie is a piece of information that our webserver sends to your computer (specifically, to your browser file) when you access a website. Then when you come back to our site, our web server will detect whether you have one of our cookies on your computer. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately. For instance, our site may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the site.

**WHAT WE DO WITH INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Interacting With You.**

 We will use your Identifiable Information to respond to requests you may make of us. We may also use your Identifiable Information to contact you and/or provide you with general information about our products and services. We may also enhance or merge your Identifiable Information with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

**Making Our Platform Better.**

From time to time, we may refer to your Identifiable Information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our websites, products and services. We may also refer to Non-Identifiable Information, such as tracking information collected with cookies and web beacons, to analyze the performance of, and make improvements to, our products. We do not sell your identifiable information to any third party mailing lists.

**WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION TO OTHERS**

**To Our Agents, Partners or Contractors.**

We may share your Identifiable Information with our agents, contractors or partners in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for, or with us.

These agents, contractors or partners are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services for Sprinklr, or services for the collaboration in which they and Sprinklr are engaged.

We may, for example, provide your information to agents, contractors or partners for hosting our databases, for data processing services or so that they can mail you information that you requested.

**To the Government or Law Enforcement.**

We may share your Identifiable Information to comply with requests by law enforcement or governmental authorities or where we have any other legal obligation to disclose the information sought.

**To a Purchaser, Assignee or Transferee of Our Website Business.**

We may also provide your Identifiable Information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this website to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat your Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**HOW WE STORE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Areas of this website that collect your Identifiable Information use industry standard secure socket layer encryption (SSL); however, to take advantage of this your browser must support encryption protection. Sprinklr will take physical, technical and organizational measures in accordance with industry standards to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. However, Sprinklr cannot guarantee the security of information on or transmitted via the Internet. Users are solely responsible for protecting their passwords, limiting access to their computers, and signing out of the Website after their sessions.

**HOW TO ACCESS, UPDATE & DELETE YOUR INFORMATION**

You may request a copy of the information we have collected about you by contacting us with your full name, email address or IP address. You may also request that your information be updated or completely deleted from our system. Send all requests to the following address and be as detailed as possible about what you want us to do with your information:

Sprinklr Privacy Compliance  
29 W. 35th St. 8th Floor  
New York, NY 10001  
(917) 933-7800

While we strive to honor all reasonable requests, please be aware that we backup our data to prevent accidental or malicious destruction of your information. Information on backup servers may take some time to be completely deleted from our system. If you request that we remove you from our contact lists, please note that you may still receive materials from us while your request is being processed.

**NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN’S INFORMATION**

Sprinklr does not direct any of its practices or system towards children. We are committed to respecting the privacy of children online. If Sprinklr learns that the information of a child under the age of 13 is stored within its platform, Sprinklr will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

**LINKS ON OUR SITE**

As a convenience to our visitors, our website includes links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The policies and procedures described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information about their privacy, security, data collection and disclosure policies.

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

We may update this website Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it, for your convenience, we will make the updated policy available on this page. Sprinklr encourages all users to check this Website Privacy Policy frequently to stay up to date on any changes. Continued use of the Website after the effective date of any change in this Website Privacy Policy will constitute acceptance of such change.
